alpha-vision.com 2019-03-18

# Privacy Policy | Alpha Vision

**Effective Date of this Privacy Policy** : October 9th, 2015

This Privacy Policy explains how Alpha Vision handles the personal information that you provide to us on our Website. Your use of Alpha Vision Website is subject to this Privacy Policy and the Online [Terms of Use](https://www.alpha-vision.com/terms-of-use/). Please read this Privacy Policy before using Alpha Vision Website or submitting personal information to us.

**What is “personal information” as used in this Privacy Policy?**

“Personal information” means information that identifies you or could be used to identify you and which is submitted to and/or collected by Alpha Vision Website. Examples of personal information include your name, your postal address, your e-mail address and your telephone number.

**How does Alpha Vision collect information online?**

Alpha Vision collects information in two ways:

  * **Personal Information You Submit**

Alpha Vision collects personal information that you enter into data fields on our Website. For example, you may submit your name, postal address, e-mail address, and/or other information in order to receive information about us. To protect your privacy, you should not provide Alpha Vision with any information that is not specifically requested.

  * **Passive Collection of Unidentifiable Information:**

Alpha Vision Website may collect information about your visits without you actively submitting such information. Unidentifiable information may be collected using various technologies, such as cookies, and web beacons. Cookies are small text files that are transferred to your computer’s hard disk by a Web site. Web beacons (also referred to as GIF files, pixels or Internet tags) help Alpha Vision recognize a unique cookie on your browser. Your Internet browser automatically transmits to Alpha Vision Website some of this unidentifiable information, such as the URL of the Web site you just visited and the browser version your computer is operating. Passive information collection technologies can make your use of Alpha Vision Website easier by allowing us to provide better service, compile statistics, analyze trends, and otherwise administer and improve Alpha Vision Website. Information collected by these technologies cannot be used to identify you without additional identifiable information and Alpha Vision will not connect additional identifiable information with information collected through the use of such tracking technologies. With respect to limiting or disabling tracking technology please see below “ **What choices do I have about how Alpha Vision collects and uses personal information about me?”.**

**In what circumstances and for what purposes might Alpha Vision collect and use personal information?**

Alpha Vision will use the personal information you provide through Alpha Vision Website to respond to your questions and to provide you with efficient customer service.  Provided that we have your prior consent, we will also use your information in order to send you information and promotional material relating to our Suite of Solutions via email, mail, phone, social media or other means.

**Does Alpha Vision consolidate personal information?**

Alpha Vision may consolidate the personal information of customers who use Alpha Vision Website. In addition, we may consolidate information in a non-identifiable form (aggregate/anonymous data) to help us better design Alpha Vision Website and to enhance our research activities.

**What choices do I have about how Alpha Vision collects and uses personal information about me?**

You may always limit the amount and type of personal information that Alpha Vision receives about you by choosing not to enter any personal information into forms or data fields on Alpha Vision Website. Other parts of Alpha Vision Website may ask whether you wish to opt into our contact lists for offers, promotions and additional services that may be of interest to you.

Some Internet browsers allow you to limit or disable the use of tracking technologies that collect unidentifiable information.

**Who will have access to personal information about me?**

Personal information can be accessed by a restricted number of Alpha Vision employees and by third parties with whom Alpha Vision contracts to carry out business activities for Alpha Vision. We train our employees about the importance of privacy and how to handle and manage customer data appropriately and securely. In addition, Alpha Vision’s practice is to require its contractors to keep your personal information confidential and to use your personal information only to perform functions for Alpha Vision.

**Does Alpha Vision share personal information with third parties?**

Except as otherwise stated in this section, Alpha Vision will not transfer your personal information to third parties unless you have been provided with an opportunity to opt into this disclosure. Alpha Vision may disclose your personal information without your opt-in to third party service providers which assist us with our business activities. It is Alpha Vision’s practice to require such third party service providers to keep your personal information confidential and to use your personal information only to perform functions for Alpha Vision, in accordance to Alpha Vision’s instructions. Alpha Vision further reserves the right to disclose your personal information to respond to authorized information requests from government authorities or when otherwise required by law. In the event Alpha Vision sells one of its product lines or divisions, Alpha Vision will only transfer your personal information to the buyer subject to your consent where required by applicable law so that the buyer can continue to provide you with information and services.

**Does Alpha Vision display customized ads through social media tools?**

We may display interest-based ads relating to information you have consented to receive if you are a social media user. Some social media companies provide a tool allowing the personalization of ads based on your interactions with websites you visit.   Please consult the terms and conditions of your social media accounts to understand their respective privacy policies and practices.

**How does Alpha Vision secure personal information?**

It is Alpha Vision’s practice to secure all personal information collected; however, the confidentiality of personal information transmitted over the Internet cannot be guaranteed. We urge you to exercise caution when transmitting personal information over the Internet. Alpha Vision cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will not gain access to your personal information; therefore, when submitting personal information to Alpha Vision Website, you must weigh both the benefits and the risks. Please remember that if you post any of your personal information in public areas of Alpha Vision Website, this information may be collected and used by others over whom Alpha Vision has no control. Use caution when posting personal information at all times.

**How may I access or correct personal information or delete it from current customer records?**

You may request access to your personal information which is held by Alpha Vision at any time. With your support, Alpha Vision will keep personal information accurate and up-to-date. You may request to remove, amend or correct your personal information. Please notify us of your wishes by contacting us in one of the ways specified below.

**How long will Alpha Vision store my personal information?**

In general, Alpha Vision will only store your personal information for as long as it is needed to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected, subject to applicable data retention periods imposed upon Alpha Vision by applicable law.

**How can I contact Alpha Vision?**

If you have questions about the scope, use, amendment, or deletion of personal information that you have provided to us, or if you would like to opt out of future communications from Alpha Vision, please contact us by clicking on the “Contact Us” link on [www.alpha-vision.com/contact-us](https://www.alpha-vision.com/contact-us/) or by e-mailing us at [sales@alpha-vision.com](mailto:sales@alpha-vision.com). Alternatively, you may send a letter to the

Alpha Vision  
400 Armand-Frappier, Ste 150  
Laval, Quebec  
H7V 4B4

In all communications to Alpha Vision, please include the e-mail address used for registration (if applicable) and a detailed explanation of your request. If you would like to delete, amend or correct your personal information and are contacting us by e-mail, please put “Deletion Request” or “Amendment/Correction Request”, as applicable, in the subject line of the e-mail. We will do our best to respond to all reasonable requests in a timely manner.

**How will I know whether Alpha Vision has updated this Privacy Policy?**

If Alpha Vision changes its privacy practices, an updated version of this Privacy Policy will reflect those changes and we will notify you of such changes by updating the effective date at the top of this Privacy Policy. Please check this site frequently to see recent changes. Without prejudice to your rights under applicable law, Alpha Vision reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect technological advancements, legal and regulatory changes and good business practices.
